Richard?
Over there is fine.
那儿挺好.
Yvonne!
I'm almost finished!
我快好了!
Believe me, Douglas, Yvonne promised she would take the day off.
相信我, Douglas, Yvonne答应过今天要休息的.
She said she had done enough work for one week.
她说她这一个星期做的事够多了.
And now she is in there with a calculator.
但现在她却又在那里用计算器干活儿.
I know. I know.
我知道. 我知道.
Douglas, don't be shy.
Douglas, 别客气.
This looks great.
看上去真不错.
It smells fantastic.
闻起来好极了.
Dig in. Yvonne!
吃吧. Yvonne!
Two seconds!
两秒钟就好!
Douglas, Yvonne mentioned you were in Chicago.
Douglas, Yvonne说你去Chicago了.
Yeah. For a seminar on selling commercial property.
是的. 去参加一个关于出售商业资产的研讨会.
It was just a couple of days.
只待了几天.
This is delicious.
味道好极.
But the flight back was horrible.
但回程很糟糕.
We flew through a huge storm.
我们飞行过程中经历了暴风雨.
I hate airplanes.
我讨厌坐飞机.
You told me you were over that.
你跟我说过你已经不怕了.
Not when I hear these stories.
但我听不得这类事.
This was pretty bad.
这次是很糟糕.
At one point, the flight attendants told us we had to take crash positions.
空中服务员一度曾告诉我们要做好应急准备.
Oh, my god! You're kidding!
Oh, 天哪! 你是在开玩笑吧!
No. And then the pilot came on and said we couldn't land.
不是. 然后驾驶员在广播中说我们无法降落.
It was absolutely terrifying.
那真是太可怕了.
Of course, statistically, it's very safe.
当然, 统计数字表明, 飞机是很安全的.
Tell that to the people in the crash position.
去跟那些面临应急情况的人说吧.
Well, to be fair, I lived to tell the story. I am here.
Well, 说句公道话, 我还是活下来讲这番经历了. 我现在就安然无恙地在这里.
But your wife isn't. Yvonne!
但你妻子不在. Yvonne!
Yvonne, we ate all the food!
Yvonne, 我们可都吃光了!
There's nothing left. You missed it.
一点都没有了. 你错过了这顿饭.